<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="64">
    <title>
        <en>Production Inspector</en>
        <de>Produktions Inspektor</de>
    </title>
    <description>
        <en><![CDATA[Production Inspector shows your productions, animals, and/or storage silos at a glance

Options:
 - Show input materials and their fill levels for production facilities
 - Show output products and their fill levels for production facilities
 - Show production lines and their status in production facilities
 - Show number of animals and space left
 - Show food levels (total and individual)
 - Show output products and their fill levels
 - Show animal health average, breeding average, and immature animal percentage
 - Show silo fill percentage, and what is in it.
 - Add an underscore to a production point, animal pen, or silo name to hide it from the HUD (_)
 - HUD elements can be shown, hidden and positioned individually.  When in the same position, they will stack.

Default Input Bindings:
Left Ctrl + Left Alt + Num Pad 8 : Reload configuration file from disk
Left Alt + Num Pad 8 : Toggle production display on and off
Left Alt + Num Pad 7 : Toggle animal display on and off
Left Alt + Num Pad 6 : Toggle silo display on and off

Changelog:

v1.1.0.0
 - Add key binds to toggle displays on and off
 - Add option to toggle display of percentages and fill levels independantly
 - Add option to show Prodcution output destination modes
 - Add sorting by name, and hiding or Production Points, Animal Pens and Silos that end in an underscore ("_")
 - Add option to limit number of Production Points, Animal Pens and Silos
 - Add option to change text size
 - Add AnimalInspector and newly created Silo HUD to this inspector
 ]]></en>
        <de><![CDATA[Production Inspector zeigt Ihre Produktionen, Tiere und/oder Lagersilos auf einen Blick

Optionen:
 - Anzeige der Eingangsmaterialien und ihrer Füllstände für Produktionsanlagen
 - Anzeige der Ausgangsprodukte und deren Füllstände für Produktionsanlagen
 - Anzeige von Produktionslinien und deren Status in Produktionsanlagen
 - Anzeige der Anzahl der Tiere und des verbleibenden Platzes
 - Nahrungsmittelbestände anzeigen (gesamt und einzeln)
 - Anzeige der Ausgangsprodukte und deren Füllstände
 - Anzeige des durchschnittlichen Gesundheitszustands der Tiere, des Zuchtdurchschnitts und des Anteils unreifer Tiere
 - Zeigt den Prozentsatz der Silofüllung und den Inhalt des Silos an.
 - Fügen Sie einen Unterstrich an einen Produktionspunkt, eine Tierbucht oder einen Silonamen an, um ihn aus dem HUD auszublenden (_)
 - HUD-Elemente können individuell ein- und ausgeblendet und positioniert werden. Wenn sie sich an der gleichen Position befinden, werden sie gestapelt.

Standard-Tastenbefehle:
Left Ctrl + Left Alt + Num Pad 8 : Konfigurationsdatei von der Festplatte neu laden
Left Alt + Num Pad 8 : Produktionsanzeige ein- und ausschalten
Left Alt + Num Pad 7 : Tieranzeige ein- und ausschalten
Left Alt + Num Pad 6 : Siloanzeige ein- und ausschalten

Changelog:

v1.1.0.0
 - Hinzufügen von Tastenkombinationen zum Ein- und Ausschalten von Anzeigen
 - Option hinzufügen, um die Anzeige von Prozentsätzen und Füllständen unabhängig voneinander umzuschalten
 - Option hinzufügen, um die Modi für die Produktionsausgabe anzuzeigen
 - Hinzufügen der Sortierung nach Namen und Ausblenden von Produktionspunkten, Tierställen und Silos, die mit einem Unterstrich ("_") enden
 - Hinzufügen der Option zur Begrenzung der Anzahl von Produktionspunkten, Tierställen und Silos
 - Hinzufügen der Option zum Ändern der Textgröße
 - Hinzufügen des AnimalInspector und des neu erstellten Silo HUD zu diesem Inspektor
 ]]></de>
    </description>
    <author>JTSage</author>
    <version>1.1.0.0</version>
    <iconFilename>modIcon.dds</iconFilename>
    <multiplayer supported="true"/>
    <extraSourceFiles>
        <sourceFile filename="loader.lua"/>
    </extraSourceFiles>
    <l10n filenamePrefix="translations/translation"/>

    <actions>
        <action name="ProductionInspector_reload_config" category="SYSTEM" axisType="HALF" ignoreComboMask="false" />
        <action name="ProductionInspector_toggle_prod_visible" category="SYSTEM" axisType="HALF" ignoreComboMask="false" />
        <action name="ProductionInspector_toggle_anim_visible" category="SYSTEM" axisType="HALF" ignoreComboMask="false" />
        <action name="ProductionInspector_toggle_silo_visible" category="SYSTEM" axisType="HALF" ignoreComboMask="false" />
    </actions>
    <inputBinding>
        <actionBinding action="ProductionInspector_reload_config">
            <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lctrl KEY_lalt KEY_KP_8" axisComponent="+" neutralInput="0" index="1" />
        </actionBinding>
        <actionBinding action="ProductionInspector_toggle_prod_visible">
            <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lalt KEY_KP_8" axisComponent="+" neutralInput="0" index="1" />
        </actionBinding>
        <actionBinding action="ProductionInspector_toggle_anim_visible">
            <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lalt KEY_KP_7" axisComponent="+" neutralInput="0" index="1" />
        </actionBinding>
        <actionBinding action="ProductionInspector_toggle_silo_visible">
            <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lalt KEY_KP_6" axisComponent="+" neutralInput="0" index="1" />
        </actionBinding>
    </inputBinding>
</modDesc>
